# **Corbin Graves**

(336) 963-1793 corbingraves90@gmail.com www.corbingravesdesign.com

My background gives me a unique mix of leadership and design knowledge that has proven to be an asset to my work. I started my career as an art educator designing in-person and virtual experiences and events, focusing on the needs and ultimate goals of my students and the communities I served. These experiences have honed my skills in building empathy and creating connections between diverse people, teaching students and adults. I discovered that I had a passion for UX/UI design.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Interactive Media Director Miami Museum of Contemporary Art of the African Diaspora

August 2021 - December 2023

- Reviewed front-end design and content updates with a team of 5 developers to improve user interface and functionality; achieved a 30% reduction in user complaints and a 50% increase in user engagement
- Advised in as project manager team of 4 developers, 2 researcher, 4 designers 2 marketers to create 4 project real world client

## Adjunct professor at the University of Miami

August 2020 - December 2023

- Taught and designed 3–6-month courses on the design thinking process for mixed-reality experiences and basics of web development, HTML, CSS, SEO, JavaScript, resulting in above average professor and course reviews.
- Conducted user experience research and usability testing to improve XR student applications, resulting in a 20% increase in user engagement and 15% reduction in user errors.
- Volunteered in designing, handling project management, and curriculum design aspects of web
  application design for the Florida Audubon Society to increase visibility of the growing dangers of
  nutrient-rich runoff and the toxic blue-green algae in Lake Okeechobee and the surrounding
  communities.

#### **Visual Arts Teacher**

August 2014 - December 2019

• Planned, designed, and implemented community 3 art shows with 2 local partnering organizations

## **EDUCATION.**

### The University of Miami,

August 2019 - June 2021

MFA Interactive Media UX/UI design

## Eastern Carolina University,

August 2008 - December 2012

• Bachelor of Fine Arts in Art Education.

### Skills

- Prototyping and visual user experiences
- Agile methodologies/ DevOps
- Human Centered Design methods
- Identifying key takeaways and synthesizing into design next steps

<ul> <li>UX/UI research, design, evaluations, and testing.</li> </ul>	